guitarparty.com 2016-11-25

# GUITARPARTY PRIVACY POLICY

## 1\. Your Privacy: Overview

This privacy policy (this "Privacy Policy") tells you about the information that Guitar Party, LLC ("Guitar Party," "we," "us" or "our") collects in connection with the operation of its website, www.guitarparty.com (the "Site") and all related online services offered by Guitar Party (the “Services”), how the information is used and how you can access and correct certain information that we may collect. 

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected from you by Guitar Party via the Site and/or Services. It does not apply to information obtained or disclosed in offline correspondence, at our stores or through other personal contacts with Guitar Party representatives. Further, the Site and/or Services may contain links to other entities' websites that are not controlled or operated by Guitar Party. This Privacy Policy does not apply to such third party websites, and Guitar Party is not responsible for the content of such third party websites or the privacy practices of such third parties. Therefore, we encourage you to request and review the privacy policies of any third parties upon disclosing your information such parties or visiting such third party websites. This Privacy Policy is effective as of June 2, 2012. 

## 2\. Collection of Your Information

You can access some areas of the Site and/or Services without submitting any personally identifiable information. Guitar Party collects personally identifiable information only if you choose to complete the online forms to contact us, complete a profile, provide design/product feedback or to request information or assistance through the Site and/or Services. The personally identifiable information that Guitar Party collects through these portions of the Site and/or Services includes your name, username, password, email address, address and telephone number and any other personally identifiable information that you choose to include in your profile or in your submissions to us. You represent and warrant that you have the right and authority to provide any information provided by you. Guitar Party may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information in connection with the operation of the Site and/or Services, including IP addresses, browser or operating system information, data on advertisements or links on which you click, and the websites that you visit before or after you visit the Site and/or Services. Such information is maintained by Guitar Party or service providers acting on behalf of Guitar Party. Other users of the Site and/or Services may be able to view your information. 

## 3\. Protection of Your Information

To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and facilitate the appropriate use of information, Guitar Party uses physical, technological and administrative procedures to attempt to protect the personally identifiable information we collect through the Site and/or Services. Nevertheless, Internet transmissions are never completely private or secure. You understand that any messages or information you send to the Site and/or Services may be read or intercepted by others. If you have any questions about the security of personally identifiable information collected by Guitar Party, please contact us at: support@guitarparty.zendesk.com. 

## 4\. Use of Your Personally Identifiable Information

Upon our collection of your personally identifiable information, Guitar Party may use such personally identifiable information internally, separately or in combination with pre-existing information, for the following purposes: 

\- To provide any requested information, products or Services;   
\- To troubleshoot problems with the Site and/or Services;   
\- To customize your experience on the Site and/or Services;   
\- To enforce our Terms of Use, End User License Agreement or comply with this Privacy Policy; or   
\- To contact you with more information about Guitar Party and its products and stores.   

Personally identifiable information collected on the Site and/or Services may be stored and processed in the United States, Canada or abroad. 

## 5\. Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose your personally identifiable information to our subsidiaries or affiliates and to third party partners whom we occasionally hire to provide services on our behalf, including support services, website services, delivering promotional materials, answering customer questions about our services and new services. Guitar Party will only provide those third party partners with the personally identifiable information they need to deliver the services to us and/or on our behalf, and they will be contractually prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. In the event that Guitar Party is involved in a transaction such as a merger, stock purchase or sale, or sale of substantially all of Guitar Party assets, your personal information may be transferred to the other party in such transaction. Guitar Party reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or legal process or otherwise requested by any law enforcement officer or agency acting under color of law. In addition, Guitar Party reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information based on the good faith belief that such action is necessary or appropriate to: (a) protect and defend the rights or property of Guitar Party, or (b) act in urgent circumstances to protect the safety or security of the public or of users of the Guitar Party’s products and/or the Site and/or Services. 6\. Retention of Your Personally Identifiable Information The personally identifiable information that you provide will be stored and maintained by Guitar Party until you instruct us otherwise, or, in Guitar Party’s sole discretion, for the longer of: (a) for so long as is necessary or appropriate to carry out the purpose(s) for which such information was collected and (b) for so long as we are required to maintain such information by law or other applicable rules or regulations. 

## 7\. Children's Privacy

Guitar Party recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. The Site and Services are not intended for children under the age of 13. Guitar Party does not target its Site and/or Services to children under 13. Guitar Party does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. 

## 8\. Choice and Opt-Out Preferences

Guitar Party does not collect your personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide it. If, at any time, you prefer not to receive further e mail communications from Guitar Party (except in connection with information, products or services that you specifically request), you will have the ability to unsubscribe from such communications by means of a link provided in every broadcast e-mail that is sent to you by Guitar Party. If, at any time, you prefer not to receive any other form of communication from Guitar Party, you will have the ability to unsubscribe from such communications by contacting us at: support@guitarparty.zendesk.com. 

## 9\. Access and Accuracy

Guitar Party will use commercially reasonable efforts to provide access to your personally identifiable information if you request such access in writing submitted to: support@guitarparty.zendesk.com. Guitar Party reserves the right to deny access to your personally identifiable information: (a) when such denial of access is required by law; (b) when granting you access is reasonably likely to negatively impact other people's privacy; (c) when such access to your acceptance of This Privacy Policy and Revisions to This Privacy Policy is cost prohibitive; (d) when your acceptance of This Privacy Policy and Revisions to This Privacy Policy is necessary to protect Guitar Party’s rights and property, and (e) when such requests are frivolous or made in bad faith. If you believe that the personally identifiable information maintained by Guitar Party about you is inaccurate or incomplete, you may notify Guitar Party in writing describing in details any inaccuracies or omissions, submitted to: support@guitarparty.zendesk.com. Following receipt of such a properly submitted written notice, Guitar Party will, within a reasonable time period, use commercially reasonable efforts to, in its sole discretion, either: (y) amend or correct your personally identifiable information to reflect corrected or additional information provided by you, or (z) in connection with your personally identifiable information, make note of any claimed inaccuracies or omissions reflected in the notice submitted by you. 

## 10\. Your Acceptance of This Privacy Policy and Revisions to This Privacy Policy

By using the Site and/or Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Site and/or Services. Guitar Party reserves the right, in our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time, without prior notice to you. All revisions will be posted to the Site and/or Services. We urge you to review this Privacy Policy frequently for changes. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services means that you accept those changes. 

## 11\. Questions or Comments

## 

Guitar Party welcomes questions and comments about this Privacy Policy. Questions or comments should be directed to Guitar Party’s privacy policy compliance department: Via email:  
support@guitarparty.zendesk.com  
Via snail mail:

Guitar Party Privacy Policy  
c/o ARC Law Group  
1388 Haight St., #101  
San Francisco, CA 94117

Validating login...
